Guide to the Robert Raymo Papers MC.214
New York University Archives
- Series VI. Annotated Texts and Inscribed Volumes
  - Three Sixteenth-Century Catalogues of the University Library, undated (Box 4)